Number one in the world, Ireland, take on the defending champion South Africa.
It's a pull B match, which could easily be as tight as a facelift.
Welcome to start the France straight away.
It's St. Louis, into the Fraiz, he's up in it.
South Africa, and they're white, Jersey.
Their third strip of this rugby will come back, looking to go wide early on.
And it's been spilt on that bottom side.
Black chosen Colby.
And Bishops, to South Africa, straight off the start.
They kick from mind and come straight down the middle.
I think back to clerk, just a little bit of extra nervous energy in that pass.
Probably overcooked a little bit.
It's going.
Normally so efficient getting out of this part of the field, South Africa.
Oh, look, he's blind.
Take him off.
Let's go.
Come on.
Look at this for a statement of the opening chase.
Fums off.
Cali gets water technique in the tackle.
Drives will answer back.
We've got a little bit of an early issue.
The Josh Bandit player here's going to be the treatment.
Jockey and other head coach took the role in 2020.
He's his position off of this World Cup to replace to a Lancaster as Lensdord's head coach.
Andy Farrell there since 2016 is an assistant, but head coach since 2019.
And he's 33-40 tests, and that is an outstanding record.
He's going very smartly indeed, but that's the biggest test of all.
Rugby World Cup.
This crowd is absolutely electric.
I tell you what.
Ireland's warm-up song today was smoked on the water by Deep Purple.
But in this stadium at the moment, it is a sea of green.
They're expecting around 30,000 Irish fans to come to start to pass today.
But it certainly sounds like more.
He's absolutely incredible.
Friends, you have to pitch side.
That you need his undown staff and will lift your time.
It's a pinch at the line of time for South Africa.
He comes away though.
For Ireland down the right there, go.
Gives him park, should sit.
Forwards looking for some work around the fringes.
Tideburn, such experience.
Play, puts his head down, does the monster man.
Gives him park here again to the left.
That's such a garrier ring rose.
Cuts in nicely into the 22.
It's Ireland now that are building their phases nicely early on.
Burn again for the second carry.
Sexton finds his full back.
He goes to Union and they call the Fox such a cunning player
with advantage due to the Irish side now.
For a long turns it's in Bundy Ackie.
He's 50th international for his country.
Ireland go to the right.
It's a big pass and a lot of time.
So we'll come to react on the wrong side.
He'll be rolling to number nine.
We'll stay with Ireland.
And early look at that Ireland attack.
The deception at play is quite fantastic.
We're ready.
We've seen those pass.
It's fizzed across the front of players.
As a defender, it looks like they're going to receive it.
And then it goes to the next man.
Keeping on their rock speed as well.
Ireland's rock speed so far, fastest in the tournament.
Less than three seconds for a rock.
And they are here to play.
Sexton will pop this one in the corner.
Can't do me a good space.
Good stood up.
I'm sure we've got a two by two.
One of the 7,000 Irish bars around the globe.
I certainly enjoying this endeavor from the Irish side.
How many?
Let's go 20 tries and they're hoping to do matches.
Four more middle.
More passes in those two games and they did.
In the hole of the last rugby rock up to the front.
They go.
Tygwer and Klumpench.
Let's hoof downfield by Colby.
Not out.
Left behind from Mac Hanson.
What's going backwards in the touch?
Happy new to me.
And so I'm going to go quicky.
Off the clock.
Spots a bit of space.
And it's an awkward bounce, but it's good for South Africa.
Currently, Ireland's the hazard.
Look out.
Reels on the inside.
Big Jesse Kirlin to the 22.
And a cleanup from DL Andy.
Through the legs it goes.
Seventh style play there from Faf the Clack.
Game back on.
Just for Vissa.
South Africa now.
They're chance to attack.
Big step.
Damian Bonser.
Does one side the 22?
Oh, I don't think so.
He's now for the spring box.
He already got it.
The Clack works the short side to his captain.
See it policing.
You got the pinnacle.
Bungie and the Nandies.
Big carry from the hooker.
Vissa again for the second time.
Ireland's wall holding strong.
Here comes.
Here's an it's event.
Man, that's a built like a Bulgarian bending machine.
To the right, it goes again.
Kirl trying to skip through.
So it's a lot better.
Not bad, dude.
To the point.
And it will be a penalty for South Africa.
What an entertaining opening.
Four minutes.
Green, front of the top off feet to me.
And our shot there.
Detour.
We just saw him.
He's getting some treatment on the ground now.
He got hit a bit.
A little bit late.
Yeah, I think James Ryan went straight through him there.
That's the one.
The eyes up to the coaching box to see what kind of...
Shots called.
Two meters.
There's the ambition from South Africa.
There's a pretty loose kick.
Did our answer a favor?
We're running.
We'll dished it back inside to Kirl who was supporting...
Ring rose with the scramble tackle.
And nearly on the pinch.
We didn't see anything.
It was furious, wasn't it?
From South Africa.
And there's a little look at a bit of afters.
So there we go.
Area which they've struggled in at this rugby world cup.
Ten out of 18 kicks.
If you use Moni LeBoc in picture,
it's a fast-to-clay containment.
It's a big pot of winning rugby world cup matches.
So the flyer from the stormers.
There's an Africa's first shot at goal.
Moni LeBoc turns the flights go up.
So the Africa have the opening points in this game.
They lead out in three-nothing after five.
Nice one for Moni LeBoc to settle himself in.
He's been backed by coach and captain.
He's only on 40% kicking.
That's a nice one to get off the board.
Six step.
Down the middle.
Africa mustard is there.
Places rugby with the heat in Japan.
Can't use it!
Fifth gift cap again,
Scotland during this rugby world cup.
Six season with the spring box.
He goes to the net.
Colby comes down.
A bunch of green joes.
Hansen does really well.
There's the right wing up for Ireland.
They have it at the halfway line.
Jamison Gibson Park.
There's scum off.
11.
Lenston in.
This starting side.
They're familiar with their team at 16.
Just to get away from the collect.
Flowing in.
Tettle the Ireland.
I'm just going to carry the right at the moment, Brendan.
No attempts to catch the ball.
He just hit that on the short pass.
Henry only players outside.
Three fascinating little tactical battle.
Ireland playing with that flat attack.
Sexton taking it right close to the line.
Against the line speed of South Africa.
It's a real challenge.
Holds his feet and still to try and play around the line speed.
After that, it flies off the line, doesn't he?
Such an acceleration.
As the scum off.
You know, it's going to kill her.
Again, they've had a trouble at Lionel time.
Two knock-ons.
First by Ireland at the line-out.
Sexton, South Africa.
South Africa scrum.
Two loose ones.
The battle at Scrum and Lionel would be fascinating tonight.
I actually thought it'd be an area where Ireland might get a bit of change.
South Africa, let's sit.
James Ryan will be making the calls in that.
First scrum, Stabilia at the bind.
Good weight to sit.
Last one at the front.
It was Detroit getting up South Africa earlier on.
Great speed.
And that one would look like it was just an overthrow.
When you're trying to try it between jumpers.
It's going to be so cool, way more cool.
And Detroit and the likes of them.
You've got to be on your money.
Any intriguing matchups we set?
Scrum top.
Scrum.
34 scrums this year coming into this team.
The battle 34, but they lost it.
One of their own against Lionel and one against Scotland.
Ireland pulled it back and went early.
Next one's a penalty.
Wait for the spring box.
Scrum.
You all came in early.
Okay, wait for the call.
I'm waiting for Stabilia.
Then I'll call set.
I'll be loud at it.
I will.
Next one's a penalty.
Wait for the time of the call.
It's up once to go again.
That's so far, I wouldn't mind a bit of that.
They'll look to rock in this one.
Take two.
Coach.
Bind.
Sit.
Keep it up now.
Jason Bobby looking behind.
That's Scrum time.
Bissett picks up.
Bashes his way up field.
They're playing.
Looks for Peter Steph to toy.
Stabilia has probably played the year three times.
Okay, use it.
That's how I play.
Box one high again.
Another excellent taker.
Then absolutely income on the ground.
Can you see that?
Yes.
We can't see it.
It's just one.
Bind.
We have the half way line.
You're on the wrong side.
You got a real quicker.
If I want to reward you, you're okay.
It's just fours on the wrong side.
Nice to explain by Ben O'Keefe.
The jackal, Bungey on Banambe on the jackal,
which is legit.
I was really happy with that call too.
I thought he was off your arm.
I thought your elbow was off your arm.
But it was even etched the breath.
Just lying on the wrong side.
them to be creating a hurdle to be playing.
We're playing, guys, we're going to keep on.
What about last scrum?
The Irish forwards reckon that they took great confidence
from that win against South Africa back in November.
Even a couple of the backs have attended the scrum sessions
this week.
So some education in the dark arts, of course, South Africa
poses such a physical challenge.
But they're also technically smart.
So this is going to be a huge challenge for Ireland.
Yeah, now there they look on.
Some of the extras.
The 11 players from Ireland, 11 from South Africa.
Completed in that last game.
Well, here tonight, 1960 was a score there.
Ireland winning by three, traditionally been very close encounters
over the top, though.
The fourth line-up goes the right for Andy Farrell's side.
A warring point for them so far in this game.
OK, this one's the way up, no leave it.
Frank Moster is at the back, yeah.
Declack for the touch line this time.
Nice clearance from the scum off.
Yes, lovely techers from Fafter Clerk there.
I managed to get his side up towards the 10 from that position.
He's admirable.
Let's keep working hard on this.
We're all concerned for this Ireland line-up, though.
And perhaps after a won't mind pumping the ball at the side line.
He said five.
Continued to put threat.
They're going to go for a five-man line-up.
See if they can get it right this time.
Pressure on Caller, huh?
25-year-old.
He's 24th cat for Ireland.
Can he find his mark?
Yes, is the answer.
Pido Mani with a great take and he's 100th appearance.
And now Flakball on the middle from sextant.
Changes direction, ring rose, throws a dummy.
Oh, the carry worth, James Ryan.
Flayers play of the Eiffrallon in 2019.
Felicia, you're real nuisance around the breakdown.
Six turn, nice dummy.
Couple of fakes and they go over the top.
Here comes Ireland now.
Beautiful bit of work, Kenan.
The fox gets very close.
Does Hugo Keenan actually was in there as well?
Can I have it all right?
Here comes the Irish now.
Kenan Doris.
They get very, very close.
That's off the back of a fabulous sequence of attack.
They managed to get the line out right this time.
And then they were off and running.
What about the throw over the top?
The pump.
And then that lovely flight ball is Kenan with the fan, the pirouette, and I'm so close.
Guys, time's all up. Let's go, please.
Speaking to Andy Farrill, pretty much.
Even he wasn't sure if they were going to be able to play that attack.
And the attractive rugby that they have played in the first two games,
given the physicality of South African side.
But it's pretty clear the intent is there already as we saw.
It's a lot of things.
We've got come back into the South African squad officially.
As a replacement for Malcolm Marks.
Good heart this side.
A great audience there from the crowd.
And as you said, Andre pull up.
Amazing addition for the show.
I beg your side, kick 22 points to the regular club final in 2019 against England.
We'll cover from this call.
Candy South Africa, it's gun time.
It's gone again twice.
It's now pinned on a yes.
Wait for my call, please.
Another early engagement identification from referee Bernadette Keith.
I don't think there's a problem when they're down-scrummaging.
At the moment, it's just the process.
Obviously, not quite OFA with Mr. O'Keeze calls or something.
But I need you to be able to adapt to a call which's slow.
I'm waiting for balance, and then you can go, OK?
That's what we felt like they were going into the middle.
I saw Green come first, OK?
Please adapt, thank you.
Often, it's because they're so desperate to meet the hit against a strong, strong-scrummaging side.
They don't want to lose that initial hit, but at the moment, they're going early.
So everybody get their line with Ettebeth in the front.
Kaleesi now in midfield with courageous captain.
Teckel!
Got his knee on the ground.
So...
Come on!
Teckel!
He pinched.
Up the middle, come on, and Teckel!
And then Ireland lose it.
We did well to stop.
So our captain...
Knee was on the ground, so Teckel.
Then you get a turn over.
You get a good turn over.
Knock on.
Can I get my wrist?
I'm going to start this off, I mean, Chris.
We'll give it a go.
There's a crisp seed from LeVoc to a skipper.
When he was met pretty smartly by Kale and Doris.
They're trying to do the hold-up.
The venture ends up in a rut.
He was got off his business all the time.
Time off.
And then Bern gets this still, and it's the off-line.
Doris, I think he might drop one close to the line.
He's...
Sheld another.
It's not going on, OK, we're doing it.
It was good defensive work.
They've been encouraged by that.
Turn over first phase.
Yeah.
The bomb squad seven, and one split on the bench.
So much chat about that, of course.
Since they used it against New Zealand in the warmers.
OK, Ireland.
Yeah, sitting at a premium on that bench with seven forwards,
taking up all the space.
I hope it's Ryan at the only lucky back to make the cut.
Jimmy.
But I love it, darling, because I think it reminds us
that rugby is about the skill set.
Not just the number on your back.
I think that's a useful thing to remind youngsters off.
You know, don't think too much about the position you're playing.
OK, so keep...
This is much just what you bring to the game.
You bring that wherever you play.
OK, we're ready to go.
Yeah, you're right.
Some opposition fans, question to decision.
Some staff is forward as well.
But as nervous as the long tailed cad in a room,
filled with walking chairs.
But it worked for them in the past.
I love having innovation.
It's good for the game.
Breaking the mold, as you've seen this, the Africa team do before.
It's creative.
OK, let's get set and then I'll call it back on.
We'll see how it goes open, of course, in this game.
Jacques Nineber admit that there was an element of risk to making seven
to picking a seven once, split on the bench.
But there's an element of risk in anything in rugby.
You could get a red card early.
So there's a risk that they were willing to take.
Yeah, you're so right, man.
That's true.
Nina Arbor and...
See it, he rushes.
The brain's trust.
Oh.
The spring box, of course.
OK.
Seven again, 19.
Played in seven of the nine rugby world cups off the clack.
Comes to Villainsup.
Played Flaf as well.
Early in the twin of Damienville, so it does really well.
Both fullbacks.
Having some strong feet.
Here comes the join frame of Etzebeth,
that takes his shot as well to the ground.
The clack.
Wanting a quicker ball for Liverpool to attack with.
Here comes Umbanami.
I'm either on the ball.
Wide ball from Flaf.
Binds Arbor's up.
The tackle low gets in as well.
It's Ireland.
Let's stop this attack.
And draw a penalty as well.
I want to think back three players get particularly fired up
when they get a turnover.
But James does really good over the ball.
He's also got an absolute monster boot on him.
He's pretty smart with ball in hand as well.
Such a weapon for this Irish side.
The defence has been good.
The opening 16 or so minutes of this game.
Let's work out on the step here, Mitch,
everyone at the front.
I saw the back.
It's in time tonight.
You've got to receive a two metres.
It's in Vilum, so I'll get his naughty feet out.
There's the turnover.
Imagine to get hand on the ball.
Look at that.
Supporting his own weight.
Nice and low.
Great technique.
So here we go.
Can.
Ronan Keller.
Andrew.
Come down.
Continue to get Lana possession here.
OK.
What's that meant to you?
It's an Irish side that 127 of 29 games in the last two years.
Only losing two in England and France.
Did I ever get?
Sit up off the mark.
I managed to work a five-man liner earlier with a bit of movement.
And that was the key.
It's good now.
Again, it's moving.
This time they come right to the front.
Get her rips it away.
Lucky.
Steening in.
What a bulldozer, but does a he is for the Irish side.
But it's an outbreak up.
That are all over this one as well.
Both sides.
20 breakdown penalties.
Sevens on the good side.
Nine.
Careful.
You've got the penalty.
There it is.
Time.
Job the bull.
The wrap on the wrist.
The faster click for rubbing it in.
We're having the penalty here.
Expect nothing less.
You've got nothing less.
You've got to get the ball.
Got the penalty.
Yeah, I agree.
So, Bondiaki coming on that hard line.
I mean, he has been ridiculous so far.
They've had too.
Comfortable games.
But in those games, he's gone from about 268 meters.
Just top of the tree.
I think he's been praised by anyone.
Is that him in their fantasy team?
Because he's been scoring points wholesale in that.
Yeah, he's a plat.
You do not look past.
Six and also clicking a ton of points for the outside last time.
LeBouc finds.
I don't see a flat ball.
Jesse Krill comes flying in.
The clack.
Again.
Nice ball on the inside.
Peter Steph to to it.
And it's the spring box now.
We find themselves on the front foot.
No, no, no.
There's a number.
It's a bit in there as well.
LeBouc.
Behind the back.
To Dielandie puts one to the ground.
And the inside set up.
He's a bulky frame as well.
The hands down the chain.
A kick through from Damian Villamser.
And he has time back to perfection.
Real celebration.
The perfect kick.
Just staying the right side of that flag in the corner.
Trouble for Gary Ringrose.
He's out of the line out.
Keep going.
To me.
Line out on.
On his line out.
Five out.
Again.
Shorten numbers.
To trust secure position.
James Ryan is accurate.
Kirsten Park moves it away.
Here comes Kellen Doris.
No.
25 roll.
Ireland set up.
Okay.
He's in the line.
Kellen's to give some points.
No, it's not.
A great pair of Ireland in New Zealand.
And that one charged down.
He was on side the whole time.
Thank you, Johnny.
That's a big obstacle, isn't it?
When you're trying to box out of there.
Portland, I keep the tears off side,
but just about right side of the line.
It's a real nuisance of nine out of time as well as even it's a bit.
In accuracy, Edline out time for Ireland could be very costly
in this game.
This is the last attack for South Africa.
That angle.
Grills coming on there.
It's really nice.
In the slider hands.
From Marnie LeBot.
That's the one that left Gary Ringrose feeling a little bit rusty.
Tried to put the big shot on Damien D'Alendi.
Not easy to do.
OK, 13 green.
Sub.
HIA.
In fact, Ringrose is going off from HIA.
Tried to hit the LNN.
106 KG or so.
In the mould of John De Villiers, you might say,
who sat behind us here in the Comtubox.
Not a bad replacement in Robyn Hinchel there as well.
He's got to carry Ringrose.
Same message, timing.
We'll close it up.
Griner just called the great Irish in the team as well.
It didn't bring his boots, he said.
Still a rugby World Cup record holder with the Irish site.
We've never got past a quarterfarmers, in fact.
We wouldn't believe that team could fall with this Irish site.
Robyn Hinchel coming in and he'll need all 70 caps experience.
Now 71 to defend this scrum.
He's got to be a good player.
The club fee is for South Africa.
There are up three nothing.
21 minutes gone.
DL Andy goes up fielders.
Daniel DL Andy within three metres.
South Africa on the board just scoring.
He just stepped to his step.
South Africa scrum taken back.
South Africa scrum.
No, it's been ripped by greenie liven.
And it's gone back into end goal.
Oh, the line of Damien DL Andy.
It's taking an Ireland player one by one.
Who is it?
Jimmy, I'm holding the block pre-calling now.
I'm pretty sure he's saying you come back against the angle.
He almost pre-called the step.
Running into Johnny Sexton.
He put a sharp good shoulder contact.
But it's come off second best.
James Lowe in there again doing a bit of back row work.
That's why we got time off.
Maybe save the one you're playing.
Because you can start afterwards.
Thank you.
Real boring time from Johnny Sexton to Captain Ireland.
One of the most decorated plays in the world.
He's for Frankie World Cup.
Yes, this guy is for Frankie Beckham.
OK, sit down.
Time's going back on, please.
Ireland, time's going back on, please.
Well, on the ball's line, his game is being played out of place.
A great tempo.
I agree, but when I have the ball on the back I'll say,
use it for the contest.
You can just go away.
No, no.
He's taken back and gone by.
Go ahead.
Shallor Lacaster.
I heard you, I heard you, Bondy.
Did you?
Let's go, there's the Marcus in the middle.
L
See the way, Marnie LaBoccu's just got his eyes, a widened at this area of the park.
When he knows he's getting the chance to create something,
just as fast-paced, energising presence in this South Come Backline,
and he's got venom set behind him here.
Go!
Bones!
Six!
The Scremble touches both sides.
Two feet.
The Clack.
Short ball.
Jesse Krill.
Very close.
Kaleesi loses it.
Ireland have it.
They're caught.
Celebrating.
No, Bones over.
The way they repel the Scremblecks,
but it's not out.
Villains are.
Big step of his left.
Get rid of one.
Does the feedback for South Africa?
Visa.
Skips master goes to Stephen Kitsoff.
The one they call the Angry Plum.
Kaleesi takes, goes low.
Downs is out of a couple.
A school has come in there as well.
I did not see him move.
It's the same piece.
The Screel, again, piercing through the middle.
What a tackle from Bundy Arkey.
Chopped him down.
Eyes on.
Get slow.
Takes the legs.
That is fabulous.
From both centres.
That was going to be a score.
Here's the turn over.
Just a little knock on in there.
James Lose.
The Ireland defence.
Keeping them out.
Just about.
At the moment.
Time is much better.
Ireland.
Good patience.
That's the call.
Come on.
Get the nice down here.
Goad.
Bind.
eme.
And it doesn't mean passing.
That would be difficult.
Yes!
Swab, left hand.
Ah,side, full noise.
Here it's that, the France, sexton.
Yue.
Utah.
HAих DIAN-Fiel.
kickdown feal by Hugo Canaan,
the former Sevens international.
Well done.
下一 world their way up the field.
bearings.
Yeah, that's lifting.
Yeah, there's now.
It's coming.
You must have good space.
The South come back to where he's starting.
Back to cover the kick.
The attack is in the back.
Ireland.
The back three of South comes up,
which then leaves that backfield space.
I actually think Hugo Keenan is so skillful,
he probably would have wanted that to roll into the 22
while his own standards.
He's been so impressive really making that 15 jersey his own.
So there we go.
Solid with Kaleesi.
So tackle.
No, your hands.
No.
Yeah, thank you.
Clack.
Money LeBoc goes to the sky.
Kirtly.
Aronsa comes down.
Oh, what a contest that is.
Aronsa wins it.
Another international sevens player.
Liding it up.
Yeah.
At the rugby world cup.
Low thought about a kick.
And then the Danny and he's been had by Williamson.
Ireland under pressure in their 22.
Josh Lander flared in the upstarts there as well.
We'll drug your player of the year in 2022.
So just.
Telling his forwards and back three to go.
No, take your step five.
Five four.
James and get some park.
Use it.
Oh, man.
You're stuck.
Take your step on the foot.
It's a bit gets closed.
Put under.
gets close puts under pressure on the ground knocked on by
South Africa.
It goes forward in the year.
Almost.
That must be for Gibson Park trying to box.
Kick under that pressure.
He's got a key and potentially playing
Iron Sea in the air there.
That causes Gibson Park to have to put.
It's got to almost go straight up in the air, which is why the
ball dropped only about 10 metres ahead of where the rock was.
Irish Chase is able to get up and make a mess of it.
That's electric to see.
To off-tries in 12 games.
He's been 10 tries.
He scored for his country.
I see a lot of games coming here next year to front to this
very state.
That's where we play.
Inside.
Start the front.
We're going to rest up the scrum.
I'll be here watching the 7th Olympics next year.
No doubt.
He's going to be kicking off.
He needs to come under.
His feet need to come under.
Your elbow needs to come up.
It's a message.
I'm not in the 22-day.
I should say.
But he is running the water for South Africa.
A couple of experienced water carriers out there.
I think people are down there as well running water for Ireland.
A couple of useful wise old heads.
James has got it.
Let's go.
We've been waiting too long.
Who said the scrum?
There's a lot of people in the back.
Are they going to fall?
No.
They're going to fall.
We're going to fall.
Nearly half an hour play at 3-0.
Say, however goodly, Ireland.
Typically low affairs.
Only once in the 117-year history of this fixture.
There's a team produced more than 50 points.
It was back in 2016.
See?
3-26.
Is a sensation in this game into the 22 for Ireland
Gibson Park
So a bunch of watchers he's flying up on the right-hand side
The right side contact numbers to the left
Porter
For Ireland can they capitalize on their break by Bundyaki. He carries again delayed ball
You know, man he's there
Much better from this Aru side a second carry again from Andrew Porter
David in 2017
Sexton crunched as he gives the inside ball to James Lowe
Porter for the third time
It's keep coming
Gibson Park shifts it to the right as Ireland
Trying to make some progress here in the 22 Sexton
Just that wall of white jerseys with the toy again
Behind the back ball trying to unlock Josh van der Fleur
Sexton over the topic goes Bundyaki yet again
Beautiful balls along the inside
Needs help
There's monsters all over it. Don't clear on it. It's for the Aru side
Porter
Nice dummy from the front of the building from then step
He play up the outside with it Vonage Gibson Park still got the pinnacle advantage across. They'll go the cross kick
Grant Henshaw
And Ireland will come back
You're always in contact to the Tecler goes to ground. No clear release
So even if he stays with his feet as the tackle assistant he's throwing the guy to ground
He has to release before he can get on the ball
Bundyaki have that out for a carry down the middle. I thought he was going to go all the way
Showed a clean set of heels
The South can defense got back in numbers and quickly so they could get off the line and start putting their
Typical shots in
There was some brilliant tackles in there friends now over up ending Andrew Porter amongst many others
We knew it was going to be a tight affair down
We've only got three points on the scoreboard so far
You get a look at the penalty ball to see he went all never released the tackle player before he then got on the ball
penalty they could sport and then okay
Very quick
There's a good news for Ireland Gary ring rises past his HIA and we'll return to the good shortly
That is great news for the Irish side. They're crowd loved that they kick for the corner
This here comes cana her now to the front
Thunderflare peels around. It's a bad hasn't
Bundyaki they most dangerous runner tonight
Still the Irish wave comes at South Africa
Gips and park to the right
Forward's quickly re-gathering themselves for the next wave
If you don't have many
Gips and Park looks both ways
Again, it's thunder flare
Ireland inching the way close up to the spring book all right beautiful play
Sexton throws a dummy
He gets so close to
To the right
Hanson
Why
It's a beautiful bit of play Johnny Sexton gets so close the scramble from South Africa and it goes wide into the hands of the
Mastasio at Mac Hanson who gets over for Ireland's first score
Seven points
If Sexton can put this one over
What a moment for Mac Hanson born and bred in Canberra Australia played super rugby for the Brumbies was actually convinced to come playing
I'll go play in Ireland by Connick coach Andy Friend qualifies for Ireland through his Irish born mother
He has another try on the big stage
Instead of that of this game
These type of games it's probably everything you dream of growing up
Well, you might have to pitch himself
Johnny Sexton
Gave it in 2000 and line in Dublin for his country
Six nations titles
And too many other titles to list right now as
Lines of the extra two does Sexton
It's right here in the middle. It's Ireland seven South Africa three
And the flags are flying at 35 minutes
It's a fist pass to James Lowe across the face of the defenders it cut out about three defenders that pass James Lowe just holding his feet good hands the catch and pass
He felt like they earned that score some brilliant attack really nice with the guys in the Emerald Green
Going for the attacking lineouts as well has paid full value
So there's seven points
Calisi hasn't forced South Africa
And Yelendi puts a kick over the top a one bounce
And just like that the spring box
Putting on the pressure against Ireland
We've seen some bullish touches from VLND with ball in hand
That was a delicate one lovely little touch over the top I don't mind that you know you've got currently iron South there he'll chase anything and he's quick
Ronan Keller
To the middle and contest it gives him park
Ireland running up field now Doris
Can on the Ireland this will help them get down the field
That can us carry from Doris
There's detour he was
Lying on the wrong side that's what can happen if you get the dominant carries so you get through the contact like that
Often leave tacklers stranded on the wrong side and there was liable to get penalized
The Irish forwards on a
52% when they gain line success so far in this tournament coming into this game for about gain line success
What a joy to have Bundyaki in the centres
What a joy to be watching him a lovely little change of pace on the width there
One of the standout performers of this world cup so far Bundyaki
What a venue for this cliff hangout
On the 15 match win streak currently sexton there's Aki again flies into the line
Doris loops around gets a good ball and a good tackle in from Calisi
Gifts in park changes direction
Thunderflare Aki again this time do your lenders there
Two of the bulkier inside centres in world
Who's it
Okay, no
Down there
Jamison gets some parts
It's come off. He's just good. It's a good point. It's a gone Tonga
Arun sir
Let's go backwards
And Damian Valimsa is there the full back to tidy up for South Africa
First receiver
You've an it's a bet
Takes in a couple Irish players
Money LeBoc on the left boot down the field
Transfer a counter here
Keenan does really well. There's a full back
So he's up in it ring rose again
Teckel
It's a bet hasn't such a porous battle at the breakdown
Big ball over the top
James Lowe puts a kick through
And this one will go up the back door
Options
See
You mentioned it during that passage down the battle at the breakdown
Who's this come
It's been so good already
So many strikes in the jackal which means that everyone technically
And in terms of their urgency is going to be so good in attack as well
Such a great contest
This is what Keenan gives it
They're roaming
Mr's good one last run out
Very well
Really good, that's what I want
You're watching the best players in the world tonight
I get this pool eight crosses over
A pool that includes
Carlos New Zealand, Italy, Uruguay and Namibia
Four of the finals will take place here
A total of 14 and 15
Go
Fine
See
Where the ball is still with South Africa
It comes on and set
Behind the back
In the box
Close and wide
To Chess and Colby
He spins out
To take on him
Score to try and drop your world cup final
In Japan last year
For Cloud
And that breakdown has been won by the final
And that comes on
I'm not for let you know that
Let's use the visa on the carry
I'm not exactly what you mean
I saw saw
Same picture
I'm watching it
He's not an easy man
It's not an easy man to take down by any stretch of the imagination and yet he got shot there
The band of clearing up sneaking in on the field and robbing it
Guys at the final team
Well there he is gets underneath but just before that was a brilliant display attacking the back bro just working together so nicely
Steven
It's pretty similar to Johnny Sexton's reaction in backplay
You can just see exactly what it means to Ireland's leaders Peter Omani gave them a stirring pump up before the game
They are here to play today
They really are and so far the scoreboard chose that as well Bundyaki
Again goes in that middle channel
Behind the back port to find a flier
Ireland back to the right-hand side they go
Porter is there
Just to skip out just with this up gets him far
Sexton quick hands
The ball is there
James Ryan catches forward
Well Ireland, Peter step the tour has it
Oh, difficult pass for a police to take and
Oh my bino just half time Ireland coming through. Yeah, and that is
The first 40 minutes gone
You're in Saint Danny North of Paris
It's the poor B-bamble at the 2023 rugby world cup when you'd be closer. It is a half-time score
She's Ireland leads an Africa 7-3 from a packed start the France
You're watching the second half between Ireland and South Africa from studying start the France at the 2023
Rugby World Cup Ireland on the left lead
7-3 against South Africa for Bundyaki with a take
Welcome to the thrilling pull B match up
I'm down the staff at pitch side that you need to use their own side great
Britain and then good time Mitch on here comes bicep or South Africa straight away. So what pinnody a quick pinch
Mustard pinnody till the line for the spring box
And hold on
Forze on the wrong side to pick the ball coming out it's a bet again in trouble for white
Yeah, I saw that and the right he was alone the wrong side the ball coming out comes out on your side
We saw that penalized in the first half the tackle line in the wrong side
I think you probably is a good call from the referee or from his assistant
They did disrupt that rugby for Ireland
Even that's the best came from a hell of a long way to make that first tackle
He started on their own ten meet lines. I think he can hit just watching you run it's got a different ball
Just I'm gonna take it quick
So he's running up full tilt and he was the first to arrive to make the hit on Bundyaki, but then
slightly earlier than that. Okay, let's start with your spaces
There he is lying on the wrong side see
disrupting the Ireland rug
It's a bit his ideal holiday isn't to the beaches of Greece but to the jump
He's coach struck me number looks on
Galahad to the back. That's a great line out from Ireland. I think throws a short bolt to he's stand apart their ring rows
And then Gibson Park puts one over the top
It's a very good kick from the Irish number nine
And it's on Africa that I kept in there 22
Let's go, please
No changes to either side at halftime so the South African bomb sport they're lying in weight
It's never evil
Confirmed it doesn't already out
The suggestion was pizza I'm on his nose
Before it went out
Maybe it's just a flock of hair
That's bound to get in the way with puffed the clack
Mustard takes is the captain Sir Colisey
Goes up field
So I've got a plan here 20-21
Captain sir to the series one of the British Irish line some of these players were playing
Against South Africa
And so throws it to his fullback
Keenan cuts back in nice either link well and then he runs into his own player was poured up
That won't count as a tackle
But Ireland still with possession playing on Peter O'Mannick
Sexton
Oh, that is a nice kick yet again
Two in a row from the Irish halfbacks
And he's saying it's touched
So he wants a piece of his line out
Whoever they get it or not
Threaded that like a needle down the touch line
There's not really much on there look at the space he's aimed for there
He's pinned on absolute six points so that bounces out
Oh
Okay, you got to stay out as we're seeing
Yeah, they don't have one 65 caps for so now we're going to interference close by in the line up
I'm getting involved now against South Africa's attack
We've got to offset Africa through
Five to cool
It's never going to fly
And
He's getting up in front of it's a better than that case. He knows he task
I'm fighting fire with fire line out time
A massive opportunity for the Irish yet
Master returns the favor
Peter Stifter to it has it for South Africa
Ever on the ball just a body know what a contest we've seen from the big men
Okay, use it hold here faster Clack plays alongside Jesse Kruehl in Japan
Downtown is the kick to the halfway line pinpoint
From South Africa the side of the half to me
Absolutely masterclass in line out jumping at the moment the way the lifters are getting
The speed with which those jumps are getting the eggs the lifters are trying them
Getting right close together so they're getting the jumper to the maximum height
Yeah, that those six line outs lost
Thrall and
Kela her proves his stats
He's through the middle
I'm to fly up
Haki
Comes in down to the halfway line for the Irish side can I ever again
Take some kicks off
Felicia comes in once the pill stays with the ball
The men in green
He's it
Sex into the right inside heat lets his forwards attack a bit more
panel the start Africa
We've got some changes coming force out Africa rg snowman's coming on so to his quagga smith and so is
John Klein who has previously played at international level for islands
So he's going to be a very interesting experience for him coming up against his old nation
Three members of the bomb squad about to
Take the field here. There's Kaleesi getting over it
Well, he just hesitated a little bit on that one because he wasn't sure if he was legal but there was nothing illegal about this
He's
He's getting his legs nice and wide to allow himself to get low over that rock
There's the light you mentioned
Fath the clack we'll line up this penalty attempt
Third most kept so I've been scum off of all time behind the lake us on the best isn't
And for eat to prepare the rugby will cut one up
From inside he's off tough to clack
Was it the uplock it's come bouncing back and flying up there was Chesson Colby for South Africa
Somehow the spring box haven't kill goes to the right and the numbers there
This may work out better for the spring box if they do score a try
Just for this up
Crunches forward the clack finds it's a bad whose picture down
That is a part real for social media
Yeah, that's a bad
That's been thrown out of the party
The house back up to chaos
How about this
The big tree up rooted
And it's going to be his last play of the match because he's coming off
He's going to be angry he'll be very angry about that will you ever add to bed
But the replacements are on you mentioned that earlier
Oxygen chair is also coming on as well
That's four replacements on the bench
John Claim out of here statement
They've got the Smith as well. There goes. It's a bad
The Viking they call him out of here slam up places rugby monster
Can you prop nice and square good. He's been left all
It depends what's it attack is off loading tight here
Made underneath the injury
RJ Simon
Since 2019 but made him press the impact on this workup ready. There's quite a smith
I love watching him play the game and all round up. You might seem sort of a few different positions today
You have the Olympian caught this man. There's Kevin Kitsoff goes off the field
So now seven most of the two plus and over again five for Ireland
Big shot from the spring blocks Ireland pick it up the back
They hit the deck and South Africa rewarded with a pounding fiber
There it is
Number 12
Sealing hands on the ground
We're going to go again it's gruntime
This is an African engine room find out
I'm in full force
The island pack of roller skates there
What a hit what a shove
There's substitutes for South Africa doing the business
Go
Fine
See
Just bought that lead so much for these two countries
We see it down far side
We're down the far side
We're going to move it over here very good very good. Okay, keep that up
We're going to keep the height of the side, the both of you
Watching the scrubs them being in them
Chasin called me right here in front of us in the far touch line, but I think the action initially at least it's going to be
Fun for the spring box
The buns club members on the field
What's the dry
Forget low-chilling is electric 24 salmon
Well, we saw we hoped it would come to him eventually
I
Know it was money in the box that delivered the goods
Chasin called me the Olympian he's magic in open space and there was plenty of it down in this touch line
The only easy run into
He dots down it's a statement score for the spring box after those two scrubs where they absolutely pushed island back towards their own tri-line
And you called it the wood from colby
Just lurking on this left-hand touch light so I reckon have the lead now 8-7
If we've been okay, sorry pretty proud just lost you just checking something
Thank you all good shot clock back on please
All good is the court
For our Ben O'Keeve
Mine in the box lines just one up
You are seat
record point score and try sis in recent times for the stormers from Cape Town
Thank you
Maybe just history comes to me after this kick
You
Look what taking his time the clock ticks
Five seconds to take the kick
Just pulls it for the left-hand side
So there we go on point 8-7
Thanks to this try
We can restart
I'll take it out of the ball a little bit for the running lines
That's the right mind
Some really big changes for both sides mark events starting to come on for the skippers
They are callisi while in and then she and if both come on for island
Thanks man. That's a lot of changes indeed
As island look to run it back
With their number eight
Kalen Doris studying psychology at university college doublet
Sexta pull back to us
Well-feeled at the Indian space ten meters
We're going to pull back down on you
Hold
I see a callisi will look
From the sideline now after being replaced
Inside
Feels kind of early to make that change
Sexta
Again to the head of the kick his full back chase as you go Keenan is there
Against villain side
The stays with the South African side
Got the clack tries to dig in
finds his fly off under pressure
Creel has it
Jesse Creel cuts in does the outside center
The clack to oxen chip behind the back he goes
The block finds
Valence of the beautiful step
With some fancy footwork for South Africa
Great presence of mine to let that one go. Creel on the charge
That's a boom sir
Fancy footwork indeed
Steps out of it. That is beautiful
You
Such a poise for a big man Damien Villains up
Good take in Henness at the replacement
Gonna clear turns it in beautifully
Dan Sheenet. He's rugby World Cup debut
Has him played for Ireland since he's put in the warm-up game
Gens England but he's on the park
On this mammoth stage in this mammoth game
Josh down is there from out here statement
Advantage
Long with the kick outside play
Offside despite being as tall as the artist out
Sorry, I just see that offside, guys
Perhaps I'll then make a couple of those changes
Don't share any in Henderson
Jamison
It's a big deal down that time. Don't dummy
Get that line out. Okay, you might go the other way
Yeah, I worked on that occasion. They can't go away with it
Someone stood in someone's hand, but I'm seeing it. Sorry
We got the pin on it. We got the pin on it here
Since now 60 more just want to
Steer this controller's another bit in Ireland's favor feels like
Asso off in the case with the spring box when they make those changes
Always does the momentum in their favor
I
Live on side on that
Charge down round though by the rock
That guy make the catch hats up to him. I think you did
Prevent a skill from this wonderful crowd
To the front for your manny
Here come Ireland now. I see releases sexton an intricate move
Brings in low that
beats one in short space
Oh my god school plan
Now rugby stop. There comes Doris again the 25-year-old car as well for Ireland. Yeah, good counter
And then it counter it
Put for Smith getting heavily involved
For South Africa
He's supposed to be some a guy bro rugby can solve any issue can pop up
We've been accuracy from Ireland
to put the pace down
This was the set put set peace play with the wrap around the little inside ball but
Southca pretty wise to it
James low making a few meters was a carrier for the back of this and Doris where the post-contact meters
Then they were inaccurate. They're still a breakdown
Big counter up to me and the South going you you really feel now they've got the fire underneath them
One point the difference on the scoreboard plenty of time to go
And thank goodness because I'm enjoying this
First off shot by
And the same's continued here. This is cool beat
Number one and two side in the world
Haven't took a lie here. It's penalty to Ireland
Oh, so back to the scotton. What a scotton
Careful careful careful careful
Oh
Guys tight hit fully overextended tight hit fully overextended collapsing
So you heard from referee
And it keeps the tight head
overextending
Oh, but
Looks like he did go down that
Too long
His body shape
Under the pressure there from
The crowd hashes and as Johnny sexted
Will drive you play every year a few years ago
Lines up a potential lead for his country
Oh
Sexton is a smooth operator
And Ireland go back in the lead
10-8
As we approach the armoff
Johnny sexton indeed no lights needed from the island coaching box
You might as well have a coach out there run around the 10-shirt the 38-year-old
So consistent so sharp he's used to winning six nations champion chips at Ireland
But boy, he'd love a world cup. You wonder is this a precursor for what's to come for Ireland?
Yeah unbelievable stat they have never got out of the quarter finals at a rugby world cup
Nice take from the Irish side canvas bd yet
2019 Japan the lost two to 48 points to 14 Gibson Park
Has to pick quickly. It's good. There's the scum off
Okay, that's better than continues here goes your five
Randy
He relieves it as Ian Henderson has a goat
He's third rugby world cup with experience he brings captain the 78 use at nine
Timing
Gibson Park we just put it right on
So Villains up Damien Villains up takes well and drives up field for the spring box
Buff the clack throws a dummy
They've got numbers wide
No handoff
He just left the tweet
Turning around the back was John Clay going against his
Team mates currently
Again, he carries hard
What a story playing both for Ireland and South Africa in his career
Kirtly Arons up with a lot of traffic in front of him
Moni LeBoc finds
Willem Sirts be left behind by Yolendi and that's frustration for South Africa
Well, there's his aerial skill
And he's so good you don't expect
Errors it and then all Tommy then all pump
The Yolendi was about to come underneath. I think on the cut line. I think Williamson's pastry with himself the hesitation
Not got the Irish crowd on their feet here. There's that to front
New crop just timing high another change for South Africa Trevor in your car
He has come onto the field for France Malhover
Another forward
Taking part
Third regular World Cup
Passing 92 is true in your county
Oh, ask me all you know
Coach
Blind
See
Alan's possession is there crowd reset
You can resound this purine atmosphere we've seen
We didn't tell you guys
The
Indie
You
Oh
Like
We're going to have to do the final round.
The final round.
Okay, time's on.
We see it.
What an interlude.
Listen to fields of Athens rye.
Bring out in this stadium.
Room.
Let me go.
If you get in reed.
Fine.
See it!
Room.
Rehak beat for four wood.
And a spring lock.
trade.
The combo of Porter and Furlong.
John's the props of the island scrum.
Hey, so water just for the kick-and-eye now.
Being demolished in this occasion.
You can see it's power.
Get underneath.
There you go Jimmy.
Box and chair getting.
How are you looking?
Sit up now.
I'm nervous.
Just there Furlong.
After.
Driving him up and in.
Takes place.
Good.
Peppy.
Run in the box.
He will start that with that.
For his country watching.
Dressed in such brilliant color.
Unbouncing.
Just to take back the lead.
Staying still.
The red number is getting very low.
There's Marnie Lebot looks on.
And successful.
Sums.
Well, a question, Mark, from A.
Sunday goal kick and Sref come to the worst goal.
Kick and record at this World Cup of any team.
And two-one.
Absolutely.
Come here.
It's just 10 out of 18 attempts.
And unfortunately, Marnie LeBot, any 40% kicking,
come here into this, so...
Do you mean I win Sums with no?
The question's about remain.
Do you see the ball as well, please?
Most of changes coming to both sides.
Finlay, Billham, Ryan Beard, and Robbie Henshaw have all come
onto the field.
O'Marnie and Ringrose, both coming off for Ireland,
while for South Africa, Deon Furi has come onto the field
to talk about me, about what's going to happen.
Yeah.
The big changes are both sides.
Who can finish off strongly?
Here comes Quachasmith.
Loves it in Green Millies.
He's not scared, he's smirked.
No, wait, wait, yeah.
First touch for Deon Furi.
We've got enough sides.
We can't be the oldest test.
If it's nothing, so they're going to get a history.
Who's the first cat with nearly 36 years of age?
And so now we have a penalty.
That, the halfway line.
Who?
OK, guys, 16. Green was offside, 16.
As he runs, he's blocking orders.
Down the right for phone.
Down the walkie-talkie.
Should say to the touch sign.
And we saw the traffic light again.
You've got a wonder.
Oh, look.
On Andrew Porter's face.
Going into that collision.
Let's pack a smith.
The grimace.
The determination.
Perfect.
The clerks can need more determination to steer this one
out right.
And boy, this team could do with it now.
If anyone, you're old.
Bands it down, field.
And misses.
That's two different attacks, brah.
South Africa keeps on in the lead, 10-8.
Come on.
Show's my point.
And on the substitution for a pilot.
Tom Echo.
And that's a change of sprub halves.
For Ireland and Jefferson Park keeps in park
coming off the field.
On Kahnemari, the very experienced Kahnemari's coming off.
119 total caps for Murray's on the field.
Now here comes Kachasmethiett again.
Into the fright.
Nicknamed by his brother.
Extinct subspecies of Zergrenan as the Kachasmethiett again.
So the electric gaming villain set.
Such a threat on attack.
John Clay.
Carries now.
Born in Krugerstorp near Johannesburg.
Do you lendy cut down at the halfway line?
Pick up four, four, five to Clagdope.
The villain set to the sky.
Low is there for Ireland.
Misses it.
South Africa.
We're in their way.
Knock on.
This game isn't it.
I watch it.
The name says had a pretty all court game today.
I've seen him running into contact.
We've seen him step around it.
On that case, you've got boots.
Like you're doing.
You're probably going to kick.
You're taking out quite a smith.
Or they'll probably take more than a swinging arm to put.
Everyone's there.
Moving forward.
Players like Smith, allowing to do the 7-1 split on the bench.
He's got an outstanding skill set home in the game of 7s.
He can carry, can pass.
And do one balls.
Goal!
I've got a smith feature in the Olympic Games.
Six.
He's going to play to cross from 7s to 15s.
One, two, three.
OK.
I'll have to go into your time.
Don't be world cup champions.
Can you trail now?
Yeah, great work.
Great work.
The only champion to lose a pool game happened in 2019
against New Zealand.
They lost.
We're only in the stages.
Carried air from Oxford and checked.
No, please.
In the place of rugby for the sharks.
Ireland.
Good turn over.
Pitch this way.
That's right there.
The top side in the world.
There are two things like that.
Very good.
Good.
Let's go.
I'm watching Cherry.
Back time by Trevor.
New County.
Tom's off.
Let's go, please.
We're good.
OK, we're good.
Time back.
Back live.
Layers down.
There's no need for that.
Getting in there.
and he's going to have to
clap, getting in there.
Toronto made the difference for his
team.
Charging that one down and deflecting
it out for this line-up.
Ireland will throw in just outside
their 22.
And Aaron, it's been problematic in
this game.
And these are important moments now.
Yeah, and she yet.
There's well-nominated for World
Rugby Breakthrough player of the
year in 2022.
Lucky is there.
Okay, that's good now.
Inside their half.
Taken back.
Hold in front.
Finds the boot of James Lowe.
Down the throat of Damien
Villains.
Will you kick all you run?
Throwes the big left foot at
step.
Fast there for a mock of
and started.
So there we go.
Working the way upfield.
Plane.
The book does well.
Here comes S.
Yes.
Stay there on the bus.
The Viking.
Sailing towards the 22.
So they're having good numbers
on the run inside.
The book.
Creole.
Peter Steph, the toy.
Losers possession.
And it's a good tackle as well
in from Conor Murray.
Do we not have a knockout
and a touch-wise?
Have ever got.
Well, it looked like you
knocked that on in the tackle.
Guys, stop there.
Stop there for a couple of minutes.
It looked like you knocked that
on in the tackle.
Guys, stop there.
Stop there for a couple of minutes.
It was touched by green trees.
A bit of crap.
My eyes are pleased.
It's been a bit late.
I'm also getting a look over.
I touched by green hand in the tackle.
Half-timo confirmed it.
Great hands from LeBot.
And a great line from Simon.
The big striding
from the second row.
I think the toy was just trying
to lift it.
It's always winger outside
and was Aaron.
It's a really big one.
It's party time.
That directly will come.
OK, we're going to restart.
Let's go, please.
Party time with the stands.
It's a little bit more tender
to the pitch.
What?
Going into the 10 minutes to go, Mark.
It's so important now these players
come into.
There was a lot of maintenance in this game.
I've seen the Irish management before, and they were saying,
yes, there is, but the consequences.
Unless they will be in the future in this competition.
Hopefully the players will be able to feel the freedom of play.
Or two points difference on the scoreboard.
One versus two.
This is going to be ten.
And it's about overbearing to stay in the moment,
stay processed, stay composed.
I don't need the full current.
Ten points, nine over Saturday as well.
The take.
for the spring box, Sean Clay, and he had him 40 matches for
Munster. Going against friends in this rugby World Cup pool
game. Advantage for the spring box. They're inside the 22.
After Clack, pushing a few bodies away.
The player comes in, here comes Cochismar, he's hit hard.
No, no, no, over here.
Island player. Island comes around the side, changes behind.
Side entry. No, it was the same all the whole time.
I don't know if it was so bad initially with the infringement
around the side in the mull, but one mull.
We might see another one roll in the areas.
And they should have looked like he came through the middle
which would have been fine. I actually thought he pulled out
perhaps under the referee's instruction, but he knows.
South Africa's chance with 10 to go.
If I'd need his heart, do you want to read?
Not accurate.
That's great.
Island line-up coach Paul O'Connor was asked before this,
whether they've thought the introduction of the Enferu would be
a weakness, and he can't have played it down, but
three.
Is it back row playing?
Yes, they do.
I'm so pleased to be here.
Transferred and gives him that variety.
It's got plenty of life experience coming to 36, but
not a huge amount of game experience at this level.
That's how much I keep at once.
Come on first night today.
Fresh up in these moments, starting to boil.
The new would be an issue when Malcolm Mox was injured.
No longer take part with the South African side of this world cup.
Island coach.
Chartered in to clear the Atlantic.
See.
Sorry, perhaps.
Big forward pack, Carling and Island.
And they're able to kick towards the touch line using James Lowe.
That is a stunning kick from the Irish wing up.
That is huge.
That was absolute giant.
Huge change coming for islands here.
Johnny Sexton is coming off the field.
Of course, he is a fan favorite.
He is a legend of Irish rugby.
He's been the heart and soul of this team all night.
He's going to come off for the last eight minutes.
Obviously, they all bite off Jack Crowley.
He's going his replacement.
Sexton leaves his country with a lead.
Can they hold on to that?
You can't South Africa up the middle.
Van Staden gets a beautiful ball.
From Kirtley Islandser who had that break.
For the spring box.
Attempts to finish her in for.
Beautiful ball back to Kotlis Mursprung at his name.
And he comes to Clack.
The box.
In check.
Steams up field.
For South Africa.
Trevon Yekani.
With possession.
That's the Clack.
Can't get it.
Island Parlin.
Who's there?
Paul.
And then it's been left behind.
Who've done field from Ireland?
A stunning steal.
And they drive back to spring box.
Jesse Creel.
Feats one.
For South Africa.
We've got turnover at the last break time.
May have lost it again.
Island.
On attack.
Here they come.
Paul Sputredle left-hand side.
Another look for some magic.
Keenan.
The fullback.
Pulled down inside the 22.
Here we go.
Release.
Clown Murray.
With his card, Eugenemon.
Again.
Jack Crowley on the field.
The cheers continue.
In Henderson.
The Osterman.
Behind the back ball.
Just held on there from Hugo Keenan.
The fox doing well.
Porter.
Tax is strong hit.
There's Robbie Henshaw.
Looks to attack.
I'm looking at the options here.
Carries well again.
The URC with Munster.
They go to the pocket.
Don't success or look to it.
They need to have a go.
Go to Scrum.
Taken back.
He's going to be a five-year Scrum.
He's charged down.
Being touched in the air.
Scrum do.
zdeoooooooooon...
тебе warm!
A couple hands on therecible.
There it is.
Touched to the UN.
The counter.
Really drunk up.
riel.
And another change for Ireland and reporter coming off the field. He's been instrumental today in that set piece. Such has been the physicality of this game. I think it's a well deserved great for him.
Yeah, it really has been a thickibit. He's on the clock.
Great shot there in the other side. It's over half-horned. It's composed yourselves in these moments.
We're just on the clock to play there. They're not all breathing in you.
And South Africa have made the bottom change in their bench. They're lowering the back.
He's on to the field, back to club coming off.
He knew Ireland was going to fit on the field at some time. He said the only back fan favourite.
Three years of dog has been saved before he moved to bronze.
It was to be interested in the second quickest and rugby World Cup mystery behind the one he sent in 2019 against Canada.
Come on!
Can Ireland put this game away?
Five minutes to play. They're leads to the Africa 10-8.
Come up. Time's off. Straight down. Don't use your head on the shoulder. It's your ball. Don't use your head on the shoulder.
It's recent. Please, Tom, we're ready.
It's tense. It's head and hands time.
You can barely watch. Two points on the scoreboard. Five minutes to play.
Ireland's setting up camp at the scrum. Five metres off.
South African line. The experience of Conomer to look into this scrum.
Coach!
Fine! Here we go.
That's the world's first.
Pell the Ireland.
You can hear the roar.
Chocol, on the line, please.
Instability.
That handsome just came up to this near side to find the crowd up.
I don't think they need it, Mac.
They're all on their feet. They're loving life.
The substitute front row for Ireland will be very, very pleased to get one over on the bot pack.
A massive moment in the game.
For Ireland. Jack Crowley.
Pivot a roll for the monster side, winning the URC this year.
From close range.
To make it a five point lead.
Pellie has his name in the box.
It's 13 points to rate.
Ireland leads South Africa.
We're three minutes to play.
Colby looks to the sky.
Is that hint of despair in this African eyes now?
Down the middle goes South Africa.
Nice lift from Ireland.
Can they close up this game?
They're carrying green.
It's a big kick yet again.
Two in a row.
One in a box.
Launches a counter.
A flash being heard and there's a bunch of green jerseys around it.
No.
Rhinoc retains position for South Africa.
Magic needed.
From some to play, Macus.
There's some Colby.
Can't get free on this occasion to the halfway line.
Two numbers, guys.
I pinch in another steal from Ireland.
And on the other side of the ball, low again, chips this way.
Who's put them on?
Colby.
He's opposite number.
90 seconds left.
South Africa's chance with ball in hand.
It hit as well.
Rhinoc wants position.
Then she waits.
The block.
It's just a creel to the halfway line.
The tackle is coming from Ireland.
Furniture, sick and man.
Hands on.
Can the advantage for South Africa?
Willum sir.
Almost got the toss away.
In the tackle, then, that eventually.
OK, you got two penalty.
One penalty here for feet.
It's not a good shot of the league.
They said coming into this, they love the pressure cooker.
Well, it's done right up now.
Money, look back.
So much celebrate is kicking in this game.
And it shocks a goal of being questionable.
It's missed a few.
It's not a good shot of the league.
They said coming into this, they love the pressure cooker.
Well, it's done right up now.
The goal is missed a few.
That's a nice notch.
He's given his pack.
It invite the platform to play here.
The drama.
I'm folding in front of us.
It starts to frauds.
Final play.
Harlan the 13-8, Thoree goes to Peter Steps to Tuype.
South Africa, warning towards the Chalant.
Yeah, Lenny's in there as well.
Tuype Bern, the Irish defender on the side.
If the Fendant's in public, isn't it?
I'm going to try to dig this out, it's there.
As they come out.
Harlan!
Have done it!
Another one team in the world.
Irish hours are smiling tonight.